University Memorabilia Collection 1988.0026
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IX: Artifacts, undated, 1891-2004
  - Magnet
    - UConn Women's Basketball Schedule, 2007 (Box 54)
    - UConn Health Center, undated (Box 36)
    - UConn Community Outreach, undated (Box 62)
  - Matches
    - Basketball (The Disc sponsor), undated (Box 20)
    - Faculty-Alumni Center, undated (Box 20:, Folder 334)
  - Medal
    - 75th Anniversary 1881-1956 (Box 20)
    - 100 Years of Women at UConn, circa 1981 (Box 20)
    - Bicentennial (CANR), 1976 (Box 20)
    - Merlin Bishop Center, 1971 (Box 20)
    - University Medal (2), undated (Box 20)
  - Megaphone, undated (Box 59)
  - Mirror
    - Audit, Compliance and Ethics, undated (Box 59)
    - UCPEA, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Mobile (pewter), undated (Box 35)
  - Mouse pad
    - 2004 National Champions (Box 43:, Folder 510)
    - Computer Center (2), undated (Box 43:, Folder 481)
    - School of Business, undated (Box 43:, Folder 482)
    - UConn est. 1881 (Husky statue), undated (Box 35)
  - Mug
    - Alpha Phi Omega, 1985 (Box 49)
    - College of Agriculture and Natural Resources Blue Mug, undated (Box 42)
    - Connecticut (glass with seal), undated (Box 54, Box 21)
    - Connecticut Huskies (white with blue paw prints), undated (Box 35)
    - Connecticut Huskies (white with blue husky; Donald "Dee" Rowe Testimonal Dinner, 1992 June 25 (Box 50)
    - Delta Sigma, 1957 (Box 49)
    - Delta Sigma, 1977 (Box 49)
    - EcoHusky, 2005 (Box 21, Box 42)
    - Department of Statistics, undated (Box 21)
    - Final Four (NCAA Men's Basketball), 1999 (Box 21)
    - Husky commuter, undated (Box 59)
    - Institute for Teaching and Learning, 1999 (Box 21, Box 42)
    - Lu's Cafe, School of Family Studies (one blue, one white ceramic), undated (Box 51)
    - Multiply Your Options: Conference for Young Women, undated (Box 51)
    - School of Business Administration, 50th Anniversay (blue ceramic), 1993 (Box 42)
    - School of Education (white ceramic, husky dog), undated (Box 35)
    - Teachers for a New Era Travel Mug, undated (Box 36)
    - UConn '29 50th Reunion (white glass), 1979 (Box 21)
    - UConn '43 50th reunion (ceramic), 1993 (Box 21)
    - UConn Co-Op (blue ceramic), undated (Box 64, Box 35)
    - UConn Football/Connecticut Huskies (white ceramic with blue), undated (Box 51)
    - UConn Huskies Basketball (blue ceramic), undated (Box 35)
    - UConn Spring Weekend (2 blue plastic), undated (Box 51)
    - UConn Summer Programs, 1999 (Box 21)
    - UConn The Flagship University (2, plastic with lid), undated (Box 21)
    - University of Connecticut (blue ceramic with seal), undated (Box 35)
    - University of Connecticut, Faculty & Staff (Close to Home, insulated), undated (Box 64)
    - University of Connecticut (blue ceramic with seal), 1955 (Box 21)
    - University of Connecticut (blue ceramic with Wilbur Cross cupola and husky dog), undated (Box 35)
    - University of Connecticut 1881 (white ceramic with blue/gold seal), circa 1999 (Box 51)
    - University of CT Libraries/UConn Coop Spill proof, circa 2003 (Box 21)
    - University of Connecticut Police (ceramic, 2), undated (Box 21)
    - University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association (UCPEA, ceramic), undated (Box 64)
    - University of Connecticut School of Business (ceramic), undated (Box 21)
    - Wilbur L. Cross Library (ceramic), undated (Box 64, Box 21)
  - Napkin
    - Faculty-Alumni Center, undated (Box 22)
  - Notebook
    - UConn USG, 2008-2009 (Box 43:, Folder 509)
  - Notecards
    - Horticulture Club (Anniversary), 2006 (Box 36)
    - Notecards, undated (Box 30)
  - Notepads
    - Make Your Mark (sticky), undated (Box 35)
    - University of Connecticut Women's Basketball National Champions (with cover), 2002 (Box 43:, Folder 512)
  - Ornaments
    - Floriculture building, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Holiday (red and yellow barns), 2008 (Box 43:, Folder 515)
    - Holiday (white), 2008 (Box 44)
  - Paddle--Fraternity
    - Blank (small), undated (Box 23)
    - Delta Chi Omega, 1942 (Box 23)
    - Phi Mu Delta (2), undated (Box 23)
    - Phi Mu Delta, 1941 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Phi Gamma, 1942 (Box 23)
    - Theta Psi, 1938 (Box 23)
    - Theta Psi, 1940 (Box 23)
    - Theta Sigma Chi, 1939 (Box 23)
    - Theta Sigma Chi, 1940 (Box 23)
    - Theta Sigma Chi, 1941 (Box 23)
    - Unknown, circa 1920 (Box 23)
  - Paddle--Sorority
    - Alpha Phi Omega (Pledge formal), 1958 December 6 (Box 23)
    - Gamma Sigma, 1942 (Box 23)
  - Paperweight
    - Links in Intensive Care, 1983 (Box 22)
    - Rectangular with seal, undated (Box 22)
      - Alumni Association, undated (Box 59)
      - Golden Reunion Club (3), undated
      - 50th Reunion C.C. Smith, 1977
    - Roper Center for Public Opinion Research, undated (Box 49)
    - Round marble with seal-Homer Babbidge Presidential, undated (Box 22)
    - University of Connecticut (glass with pewter base), undated (Box 59)
  - Pen case (wood, University of Connecticut), undated (Box 44, Box 49)
  - Parking Pass, 1992-2011 (Box 36)
  - Pen/Pencil
    - Ballpoint (in case), undated (Box 30)
    - Ballpoint: Audit, Compliance and Ethics (3), undated (Box 59)
    - Charles Lewis Beach Society ball point pen in case, undated (Box 30)
    - Division of Athletics, undated (Box 36)
    - Highlighter (yellow), undated (Box 30)
    - Holder (Audit, Compliance and Ethics), undated (Box 59)
    - Pencil (Green, Summer Programs), undated (Box 30)
    - Pencil case (zippered plastic), undated (Box 59)
    - Presidents Climate Committment (signed by UConn, March 25, 2008), 2008 March 25 (Box 59)
  - Picture Frame
    - Silver, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Silver and blue, undated (Box 51)
  - Pillow (needlepoint seal), undated (Box 35)
  - Pipe, 1920 (Box 22)
  - Placemats, undated
  - Plaques
    - Human Rights Advocate, HRH Princess Irene of Greece, 2002 May 16 (Box 51)
    - Men's Basketball Championship Floor (4 styles), 1999 (Box 34, Box 33)
    - Men's First NIT appearance from South Windsor, CT, Rotary, 1974 (Box 59)
    - UConn (wood), undated (Box 59)
    - UConn Club (blue on white), undated (Box 46)
  - Plaster model for external art (Center for Undergraduate Education Building), undated (Box 46)
  - Plate
    - 75th Anniversary, 1956 (Box 24)
  - Pocketknife
    - School of Engineering, circa 1999 (Box 22)
  - Pom Pom, circa 2001 (Box 22)
  - Ponytail holder (basketballs), undated (Box 59)
  - Postal cancellation (Women's basketball), 2003, 2004 (Box 23)
  - Postcards
    - UConn Pride!, circa 2008 (Box 43:, Folder 511)
  - Posters
    - Fall Carnival, undated (Box 53)
    - Women's Basketball Championship, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Convocation Celebration, undated (Box 53)
    - Mike's Bus (Oversize OS)
    - Silent Auction of Community School of Art, undated (Box 53)
    - Iraq i Exhibit, undated (Box 53)
    - Fort Trumbull, undated (Box 53)
    - Student Government Flyers, undated (Box 53)
    - How to find a book, undated (Box 23)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003-2004 (Box 42)
    - Women's Basketball (signed), 2011-2012 (Box 53)
  - Quill
    - With nib, undated (Box 25)
    - Without nib, undated (Box 25)
  - Rain meter (CANR), undated (Box 51)
  - Ruler (UConn Transportation Dept.), undated (Box 30)
  - Geno Auriemma's Sauce Jar, undated (Box 54)
  - Seat Cushion (folding), undated (Box 30)
  - Sign
    - I.G. Davis Memorial Library, undated (Box 22)
    - Quiet, Please This is the University Library, undated (Box 22)
  - Stamp (metal), undated (Box 55)
  - Stein (beer)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, 1959 (Box 49)
    - Tau Beta Sigma, 1991 (Box 50)
    - University of Connecticut (miniature), undated (Box 59)
    - Phi Sigma Sigma, 1964 (Box 59)
  - Stickers
    - Centennial, University of Connecticut (2), 1981 (Box 50)
    - Connecticut Agricultural College (triangular), undated (Box 43:, Folder 483)
    - I like Mike, 2008 (Box 43:, Folder 516)
    - If you think education is expensive....try ignorance!, University of Connecticut, circa 1981 (Box 50)
    - UCONN, undated (Box 64, Box 50)
  - Suitcase (Freshman Orientation Weekend), circa 1993 (Box 56)
  - Tassel (Commencement), 2006 (Box 35)
  - Tea Set (associated with Honors Program)
    - Silver (two pots, cream, sugar, ladle), undated (Box 50)
    - Tray (silver tea set), undated (Box 23)
  - Tin (large), undated (Box 47)
  - Waste Basket
    - NIT Men's Basketball Championship, 1991 (Other Level 3)
  - Wind chime, undated (Box 51)
  - Tile (framed, Jonathan), undated (Box 59)
    - UConn football, 2004 (Box 59)
  - Tea towel
    - Huskies (white lettering on blue), undated (Box 59)
    - University of Connecticut (Human Resources), 2012 (Box 64)
  - Wall hanging (lace Huksy with pins), undated (Box 59)
- Series X: Commencement materials, 1884-
  - 1884 (Box 38:, Folder 350)
  - 1891 (Box 38:, Folder 351)
  - 1892 (Box 38:, Folder 352)
  - 1895 (Box 38:, Folder 354)
  - 1896 (Box 38:, Folder 355)
  - 1899 (Box 38:, Folder 356)
  - 1900 (Box 38:, Folder 357)
  - 1901 (Box 38:, Folder 358)
  - 1902 (Box 38:, Folder 359)
  - 1903 (Box 38:, Folder 360)
  - 1904 (Box 38:, Folder 361)
  - 1905 (Box 38:, Folder 362)
  - 1906 (Box 38:, Folder 363)
  - 1907 (Box 38:, Folder 364)
  - 1908 (Box 38:, Folder 365)
  - 1909 (Box 38:, Folder 366)
  - 1910 (Box 38:, Folder 367)
  - 1911 (Box 38:, Folder 368)
  - 1912 (Box 38:, Folder 369)
  - 1913 (Box 38:, Folder 370)
  - 1915 (Box 38:, Folder 371)
  - 1916 (Box 38:, Folder 372)
  - 1917 (Box 38:, Folder 373)
  - 1918 (Box 38:, Folder 374)
  - 1919 (Box 38:, Folder 375)
  - 1920 (Box 38:, Folder 376)
  - 1921 (Box 38:, Folder 377)
  - 1922 (Box 38:, Folder 378)
  - 1923 (Box 38:, Folder 379)
  - 1924 (Box 38:, Folder 380)
  - 1925 (Box 38:, Folder 381)
  - 1926 (Box 38:, Folder 382)
  - 1927 (Box 38:, Folder 383)
  - 1928 (Box 38:, Folder 384)
  - 1929 (Box 38:, Folder 385)
  - 1930 (Box 38:, Folder 386)
  - 1931 (Box 38:, Folder 387)
  - 1932 (Box 38:, Folder 388)
  - 1933 (Box 38:, Folder 389)
  - 1934 (Box 38:, Folder 390)
  - 1935 (Box 39:, Folder 391)
  - 1936 (Box 39:, Folder 392)
  - 1937 (Box 39:, Folder 393)
  - 1938 (Box 39:, Folder 394)
  - 1939 (Box 39:, Folder 395)
  - 1940 (Box 39:, Folder 396)
  - 1941 (Box 39:, Folder 397)
  - 1942 (Box 39:, Folder 398)
  - 1943 (Box 39:, Folder 399)
  - 1944 (Box 39:, Folder 400)
  - 1945 (Box 39:, Folder 401)
  - 1946 (Box 39:, Folder 402)
  - 1947 (Box 39:, Folder 403)
  - 1948 (Box 39:, Folder 404)
  - 1949 (Box 39:, Folder 405)
  - 1950 (Box 39:, Folder 406)
  - 1951 (Box 39:, Folder 407)
  - 1952 (Box 39:, Folder 408)
  - 1953 (Box 39:, Folder 409)
  - 1954 (Box 39:, Folder 410)
  - 1955 (Box 39:, Folder 411)
  - 1956 (Box 40:, Folder 412)
  - 1957 (Box 40:, Folder 413)
  - 1958 (Box 40:, Folder 414)
  - 1959 (Box 40:, Folder 415)
  - 1963 (Box 40:, Folder 416)
  - 1964 (Box 40:, Folder 417)
  - 1967 (Box 40:, Folder 418)
  - 1968 (Box 40:, Folder 419)
  - 1969 (Box 40:, Folder 420)
  - 1970 (Box 40:, Folder 421)
  - 1971 (Box 40:, Folder 422)
  - 1972 (Box 40:, Folder 423)
  - 1973 (Box 40:, Folder 424)
  - 1974 (Box 40:, Folder 425)
  - 1975 (Box 40:, Folder 426)
  - 1976 (Box 40:, Folder 427)
  - 1977 (Box 40:, Folder 428)
  - 1978 (Box 40:, Folder 429)
  - 1979 (Box 40:, Folder 430)
  - 1980 (Box 40:, Folder 431)
  - 1981 (Box 40:, Folder 432)
  - 1982 (Box 40:, Folder 433)
  - 1983 (Box 40:, Folder 434)
  - 1984 (Box 40:, Folder 435)
  - 1985 (Box 40:, Folder 436)
  - 1986 (Box 40:, Folder 437)
  - 1987 (Box 40:, Folder 438)
  - 1988 (Box 40:, Folder 439)
  - 1989 (Box 40:, Folder 440)
  - 1990 (Box 41:, Folder 441)
  - 1991 (Box 41:, Folder 442)
  - 1995 (Box 41:, Folder 443)
  - 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 444)
  - 1998 (Box 43:, Folder 480)
  - 1999 (Box 41:, Folder 445)
  - 1999 (Box 52:, Folder 526)
  - 2000 (Box 52:, Folder 527)
  - 2001 (Box 52:, Folder 528)
  - 2003 (Box 41:, Folder 446)
  - 2007 (Box 52:, Folder 529)
- Series XI: 125th Anniversary, 2006-2007
  - Book bag (2) (Box 45)
  - Dairy club milk bottle (Box 45)
  - Fliers, clippings, press release (Box 45)
  - Frisbee (2) (Box 45)
  - Husky dog with birth certificate (Box 45)
  - Husky Trail placque (Box 45)
  - Napkins, ticket and book mark (Box 45)
  - Pin (Box 45)
  - Posters (small, mounted), 2006 (Box 45)
  - Pup Quiz paint brush (2) (Box 45)
  - Scrapbook (Box 45)
  - T shirt (2) (Box 45)
  - UConn Traditions (Box 45)